Yeah, Joe's town's very set up for
natural disasters just because it's such
a pessimistic town with the hospitals,
fire stations, police stations. What an
easy job Simon must have had there.
Already had this all implemented, but
not working. No less than I would expect
from Joe. It's just full of bugs, not
properly designed. So maybe what I'll do
is I'll just blindly accept everything
cuz I have such faith. One of my pet
peeves with Bolt is as you start
building the file and it gets to four,
five, 600 lines, it takes an age to if
you wanted to change it one or two
lines, it has to rewrite the whole thing
out. Earthquake frequency 10% chance per
day of an earthquake occurring, which in
a in real life would be very scary.
You're listening to the AI native dev
brought to you by Tesla.
Hello and welcome to another AI Native
Dev episode. And this is actually a part
two of our episode following on from
last week's episode where both Joe and I
created a couple of applications. One
using base 44, one using bold new from a
challenge that Macy gave us to create a
tiny town simulator application. Now,
this time, what we're going to do this
time around is we're going to swap that
application with each other. So, I'm
going to use the creation from Joe,
which was the Tiny Town simulator from
Bolt. And Joe's going to take my
application that I created using Base
44. Joe is going to try and make an
alteration, a new feature edition using
Windsurf, and I'm going to do the same
to Joe's application using cursor. The
trick is, of course, we don't know what
that feature is going to be until Macy
provides us to it live on the show. You
don't necessarily need to listen back to
the previous episode, but it's a great
way of seeing these tools, B4 and Bolt.
New in action in creating the challenge
applications to this state, but like I
say, you don't need to watch them to
enjoy this episode. Now, there will be a
lot of screen sharing happening as Joe
uses Windsurf and I use cursor. Like I
said before, you don't need to if you're
only listening via the podcast like
Apple podcast or Spotify and so forth
and you don't have access to the
visuals. We will be narrating what we're
doing. So you'll be able to hear the
things that work, the areas that we have
problems with. And at the end, we'll
have a nice comparative talk about what
worked and what didn't with all the
various tools. But if you are watching
on YouTube, that is probably the best
way to watch the episode as you'll be
able to see exactly what the tools are
doing on the show. But you'll enjoy it
both ways. Here we go into the episode.
Enjoy it. He's got a copyright. He added
a copyright at the bottom. He's got a
copyright. I know. Oh, all these things.
So, looking at this, it actually looks
surprisingly similar to what I created.
I think he was just as blas with his did
he write five words as his first prompt?
He actually didn't. He didn't. Many more
than that. That's interesting that we
actually have very similar outputs in
terms of the kind of things with
happiness, population, residence.
Looking at it, he has residents, but he
has no roads. He has no industry. His
world, his town is just basically a
place where people live and have
incidents, whether they're police
incidents, fire incidents, or hospital
incidents. That's Joe's world. Well,
that's not fair. There's a community
center. is the as a convenience center
where people can have incidents together
as a community. All right. Cool. Cool.
So, I think we're I think we're ready
for our next session, right? Our next
feature. Yes. So, I am going to give you
an edit. Joe is going to have the same
edit to make on your code. But again,
this is about your imagination mostly.
Okay. Thank you very
much. Look at this. So, yeah. So Macy's
Macy's handed me another envelope. Let's
see what I need to change. Add natural
disasters at least two. Okay, I think
this is this is something which is
very reasonable, very easy to add
actually, particularly with cursor.
What's Joe using? Joey's using Windsor.
Joe's using wind. Yeah, I think that'll
be quite similar. My gut feel is I could
have done this easier from base 44
actually with such a change. So that's
interesting. Although that said, yeah,
Joe's town's very set up for natural
disasters just because it's such a
pessimistic town with the hospitals,
fire stations, police stations. Okay, so
let's just let me familiarize myself
first of all with Joe's very basic UI
here. Oh, I need more money, do I? Okay,
so I can add maybe Okay, I can add two
houses, a hospital, and a fire station.
So, we don't have enough for general
amenities. This reminds me of Beijing
steak where I'm from. But let's let's
leave that. Oh, look. I can just adv I
can just keep advancing like that. Where
are you getting the money from? It's a
good point. Um, so who works at the
farm? Yeah, it's true. So, this is I'm
going to add a bunch more things and
hopefully I'm hoping there'll be some
some state which is I'm not sure.
Probably not. I'm going to have to do
this every time, aren't I? Okay. Right.
First thing I'm going to do is change my
budget. And so let's go to cursor. I'm
actually probably do I start with
understanding how the code is organized.
Do I even bother looking at the code or
shall I just jump straight in? I can see
some obvious things. Okay, you have a
cell obviously a game board with various
cells, number of game controls which are
advanced day and things like that. So I
probably actually it's surprisingly
reasonable reasonably easy just to do
you feel that way cuz it's very similar
pos very very similar to mine possibly
but I feel like it's just probably the
naming of I'm very used to actually the
way Bolt kind of structures the way it
does things which is how like how is it
different? No, it's not different. It's
very similar to how I expect it to be or
how would it be different if I was to
build it? It's it seems very reasonable.
I guess perhaps it shows how many games
I've probably tried to build with Bolt,
but to have that game board, game
controls, event system. Okay, so maybe
this is interesting. It's got an event
system. Oh, no. This is just this isn't
a natural disaster event, is it? That's
just something happens on the board.
Okay, so I guess what I want to do is
first thing I want to do and I'm
actually looking forward straight away
using cursor. The one thing I'm looking
forward to is just the speed at which
things can change. Completely different
to obviously base 44. So, I'm just going
to say first of all, give me I don't
know 15,000 uh 15,000 budget to start
with. And actually, I'm doing this via
cursor where actually I pretty much
could just could just do this myself,
but because I'm not familiar with the
code. Oh, actually, no. I probably want
a ton more. Let's just set that to 25
myself. Okay. Next thing I That's really
nice. Sorry, just to point out that it's
like actually just listed for you the
cost of things. Yeah, that's true.
Actually, good context. Yeah, extremely
relevant to the change you're making.
Yeah, that's very true actually. And 25,
even looking at it, let me see if 25 is
the default six. Actually, what I'll do
is I'll ask I'll also say I'll say set
the game board up with the default five
houses plus one of each other building
so that I have a
initial template. Actually, I'll say set
the game board up randomly, right? Yeah.
Yeah. Just so it's slightly different
every time. But now I can have some
natural disasters that I don't assuming
this is this will be reset every single
time. Actually, it's set it up not
randomly at all. It's set up randomly
the first time. View, it's just so much
easier for me to parse than the
prototyping tools where things just
happen. Yeah. And actually, what I Yeah.
The one nice thing that I like here is
typically with Bolt, I assume B 44, I
didn't actually even look at the code
with B 44. I assume it's going to be the
same where it just rewrites the entire
file. One thing I really hated with
Bolt, one of my pet peeves with Bolt is
as you start building the file and it
gets to four, five, 600 lines. It takes
an age to if you wanted to change one or
two lines, it has to rewrite the whole
thing out. Why I love this kind I don't
even know what's changed at that point.
So I love this. So I can accept that.
Oh, it set me in a population of 100.
Nice. Going back to 15,000. I'll accept
that. I'll accept that. Welcome to Tiny
Town. Your starter. Oh, look at that.
Because I guess it's my starter. I've
got a starter town. It's interesting
though cuz it's very much understanding
what I want. Okay. It's not totally off.
So, let's let's restart this. Oh my god.
Did you see that that call out? What is
this? A music event is being organized
at the community center at 34. Oh, okay.
Zero indexed it. So that's So that's
actually four, five. Is it flashing? Oh
my god. That you see that? Yeah. Yeah.
So for those just watching this, an
emergency is happening and it's a music
event is being organized. I don't know
how I need to respond other than buy a
ticket. But my response was that it
happened. A music event was happening.
It was a great success. Interesting.
Okay. I'm glad you contained that
emergency. Yeah. I don't know if the
police were involved or the fire station
were involved in that emergency. Okay.
What happened? Why is that not resetting
my town? Okay. Oh, do I need to build
that again? See, I'm not a very good
JavaScripty person. No, I don't. I feel
like preview is a bit different as well.
Oh, really? Oh, do I just need to do an
npm run from here now that it's built?
It's just a preview. So, can I ask what
kind of natural disasters are you
considering? See, I'm thinking back into
Sim City. So, I want to see the What was
the Wasn't there like an alien attack or
a massive alien attacks? Let's go for
the Let's go for the pure natural
disaster. So, let's go flood or fire or
that kind of stuff. Okay. It hasn't
added my stuff to the starter stuff. My
starter stuff. Yeah. So, let's add some
stuff in. Oh, actually that's not really
helped. Let's say Okay, I want a natural
disaster to occur. Actually, no. Let's
just say randomly. It should occur on
average once every 10 day. No, 5 days.
Just so we don't have to wait too long.
This is a horror town. Yeah, absolutely.
So, it's going to create a random
natural disaster system. It's going to
modify the advanced day in the chaos
manager function to include the feature.
Okay, fine. 20% of chance. Oh, it's
doing them itself. Look, a wildfire,
which is severity 8, a health emergency
seven, and a crime wave. Each disaster
is randomly assigned to a building in
your town. Perfect. A disaster
becomes a disaster affects town stats.
Impact disasters will affect your town's
happiness, safety. Disaster will add an
element of challenge and
unpredictability to your town. Okay, so
it's done that. There is something that
I feel should be included, but I wonder
what you think. Go on. It should spread.
Oh yeah. Responded to it should be
spreading. The disaster
disaster should spread to
neighboring Is that the US spelling? I'm
being really kind to our listeners. US
that is the US. Very kind to the
neighbor neighboring neighboring
buildings or closest buildings, I guess,
if they're not neighbors. Kind of
depends on the thing, right? If a fire
is spreading, probably the houses should
disappear. But then if it's like a crime
wave, maybe they just don't make you any
income or something. Like there's got to
be like a consequence. Yeah. Let's keep
it I'm gonna keep it simple for now just
to see if we can create a disaster and
have it spread and then we'll do both
impact and resolution. What is a
professional? I know, right? This is
professional by coding. Can you can you
tell I was a a coder before years ago?
Okay. What's it doing there? Wow, that
was speeding. It's it is this is what I
love about this. Like for me, there's
two types of AI tool. There's the type
of AI tool that does a lot which and you
don't care and you care more I guess
about overall accuracy. No, it's not
even that. You do care about more
accuracy there because you're not going
to look at the code as much. Whereas
here, I want to review it. So speed is
an important thing. So it's doing
closest building or neighboring
buildings, which is fine. Closest
building and neighboring buildings is a
bit weird to separate in my opinion.
Yeah, actually there probably is no
need, is there? That Yeah, I feel like
there's a little tendency there, but
fine if it works. Let's see if it works
first and then we'll actually No, I care
about code now. I feel like I I'm in the
code now, so I want to do that. I say
actually, is that bad to start?
Actually, I don't need We don't
need
neighboring buildings. Um, closest
should suffice because because if
they're neighboring, they'll be closest
anyway. So, let's we'll save this
rebuild, I guess, if that's the if
that's the thing we need to do. Okay,
let's rebuild. Please, I'm sure people
will tell me if I don't need to do that,
but I'm a Java developer myself, so this
is just hurting my brain to feels like
the path of least to do this. Yeah,
absolutely. This is the classic Maven
clean, Maven build, Maven install.
Oh gosh, I clicked twice. If I respond
to emergency, do you think it will say
it's been a great success?
Yeah. Oh no, it's resol it's
selfresolving.
Oh, thanks to the nearby hospital, it
says. Oh, look. Oh my god. Again, there
are
illnesses happening where my buildings
aren't. This is a respond to
emergency. Okay. Too soon. So, let's
let's go. There is a fire. It's just
going to be a disaster cuz you have no
fire departments. Oh, good point. Let me
carry Let me carry that on then.
a wildfire
response. Fire under control, but
response was slow. Okay, so that's not
much of a consequence, is it? Let's fix
this. Um, so let's say disasters, first
of all, can only occur on buildings that
exist. Empty spaces cannot have
disasters. Then let's say I'm going to
do this just all as one prompt.
Disasters can't be auto resolved. The
user must perform an action to fix the
issue. The relevant disaster recovery
service
recovery service must be
present to to resolve the disaster. For
instance, a fire needs a fire station on
the map to be resolved. Now, could you
build one if it wasn't there during the
fire? Yeah, could do. That's a that's a
very realistic way of dealing with
things. If there's a real fire, we'll
just have to wait the 6 months to build
a fire station and then we can put the
fire out. Yeah, that seems reasonable to
me. That is such LLM logic by an LLM
built it down. I don't know what your
experience is with think particularly
with curs things like this whereby I'm
actually asking for three very different
changes to happen in real life. I would
probably ask for one at a time and make
sure each one is happening as I would
like. But given I have I think three
four minutes left, this is kind of like
how I do this. And you know what? I'm
just going to blindly accept everything.
Yeah, I agree. that wouldn't necessarily
It's interesting though because when
you're working on real software,
deciding on the things you want to be
changed and the way that you want them
to be changed is the bulk of the work.
Yeah. Yeah. So, it's interesting. The
other thing is I've asked it to by
default add buildings for me. It hasn't
done that. I'm just glossing. I'm I'm
still doing it manually. Yeah. It's lost
it somewhere along the way. So, let me
add let's not add a residence is ready
to party. Four people. You don't know,
right? And let's add a community center.
A crime wave has hit the town. It's Oh
my god. It's happening across two
buildings. Let's not respond to it.
Let's Oh, I can't advance to the new
day. So, I have to respond. I've told
you I can't. That's interesting. So,
it's resolved it. So, a couple of things
I want to do. It shouldn't be able to
cuz I didn't have a police station.
Yeah, I was able to resolve a crime. I
wonder if it's going to take me
literally here or whether it's assuming
this is the app. I was able Yeah. I was
able to resolve a crime without a police
station. This should not be
possible. Also, I want to
advance to next day even if a
disaster is in progress. Please start
disasterers
uh in one building only cuz did you
notice it did it across two buildings
and that annoyed me?
So I've made some changes and we'll see.
Now you have a little bit of an
advantage with this edit because Joe
already So he did he intentionally add
disasters? He did not intentionally add
disasters but he did add the concept of
events. I see. Okay. You are benefiting
from that system. On the other hand, his
code was a lot more buggy. Oh, really?
So, I think you've had more trouble in
these little iterations, but that you've
got a little leg up. I think we'll see
how he does. Oh, no. I still forgot to
add these residences. So, let's add a
few buildings. In fact, I'll add a few
more as well. Let's advance. Right. A
crime wave has hit the town. I'm still
not able to in the community center. Oh,
interesting. I'm still not able to
advance to the next day. Okay. So, let's
respond. I feel like this is really
frustrating now. Yeah. This is what I
have experienced in the past whereby
I've I continually have to ask again and
again for the same thing. Kind of it
just tops out at some point. at some
point you're no longer able to make
progress and it seems like that's true
across tools even. Yeah, it's
interesting actually. It's saying
removed defined closest buildings and
that functions are no longer needed.
They absolutely are still needed. If I
was to do this properly, I would
probably make much smaller changes at a
time. So, this hasn't been successful. I
thought this would be much more
successful than it is. This hasn't been
as successful as I think it could have
been because I think I would probably
ask it to do much smaller things and
validate that it's doing it. I think had
I have asked Bolt or probably Base 44 to
do these things, it would probably be
more successful at doing them.
Interesting. That's my gut feel. Yeah, I
quite fancy trying that afterwards. But
yeah, I feel like I've failed at this at
this second at this second. See, I think
you've done fine. like you have made
some interesting changes and I always
think back to four years ago. Imagine
showing someone this technology. Of
course, that's not that's not what the
people want to talk about, but it's
still it's amazing that you didn't touch
any code here. No, you took prototype
code from a different tool. Yeah. You
like grocked it and made some and
debugged it and made some pretty
fundamental changes. Do you know from a
confidence point of view I feel way more
confident. I felt way more confident at
the start of this session than I did
than I do now. I felt, oh wow, this
actually works. Whereas now I look at it
and I feel, oh, actually none of this is
truly working. And I think what possibly
would have been better, not so much
having a plan of action necessarily, but
I would want what I would probably
initially do is create some quality
plan. And I would want to make sure that
every component is doing what I need to
do because the problem is I'm trying to
build on something that isn't stable
right now. And so I feel like I would
need that to be fully stable. And then
we're giving cursor a hard time here
perhaps. And it's not cursor that's
necessarily causing a bunch of these
problems. It's actually that the base,
the platform that I'm building it on,
this initial code base. And this is no
no less than I would expect from Joe.
It's just full of bugs, not properly
designed. And I feel like I would need
to I would need to bolster a lot of
those components. I'm really mean to to
Joe and I. We're gonna I need to bolster
a lot of those to make sure that they're
better uh more resilient. Yeah. And then
when I ask her to do stuff, it would
actually have a far better chance of
being able to do those things. Yeah,
that's my gut feel. But I still love the
interaction that I'm having here. It's
just the frustration of going from this
to Yeah, the death loop of do this.
Sure, I've done it. And then you go to a
production production, but you go to the
wrong environment. And guess what? It's
still not done. Great attempt. Let's get
Joe in here to learn more code. Yeah.
Yeah. Can I stay in here while that
happens? I can. Awesome. Awesome. Here
we go. Hello, Joe. Welcome back. Thank
you. We have got Simon's project up and
running. We learned something about base
44 just now, which is which is what?
which is that it seems to use itself as
a like a data store, which is an
interesting approach, but we couldn't
figure out how to get authentication
working. It's a super closed system.
Like it was really hard to get this to
run locally without authenticating to
base 44, which is Yeah, it seemed to
want to send you back up to their app,
which sort of defeats the purpose of
working locally. And then when it did
that, it gave an error which I assume is
because the authentication was kicked
off from my local copy which their
servers didn't want to accept.
Interesting setup. So we did some
prompting within base 44 to try and
detach itself from itself and remove
authentication.
So far this has seemed to be successful.
Maybe we did something wrong. Who knows?
Some similarities off the bat to your
town. Yeah, super interesting. So I've
created a town here called Joe Town and
really fascinating to see. Obviously, I
don't know how Simon prompted this, but
fascinating to see that we've ended up
with similar elements like treasury is a
word that I didn't use in my prompt at
all. Um, interesting to see that it's
arrived here also. And yeah, the
happiness meter all very similar. The
same grid format, but I see there's some
additional features that I don't have.
Also, this sort of day iteration is
automatic, I noticed, which is a nice
touch. Simon's got roads, and a key
thing here seems to be that he's got
properties of each of these things. So
some things are going to make people
happier, some things are going to cost
money, which is interesting. I didn't
really I think in mine if it worked,
money would just go up. There wasn't any
cost to anything. So it's it's
potentially a bit more realistic. You
could say how they like to me like just
the grid setup is strikingly similar.
Very strange. I didn't prompt for a grid
necessarily. I don't know if Simon did,
but interesting. But it almost seems
like we've got the same number of items
in the grid as well. So there's some
something around like underspecifying
your prompts. It's going to fill in the
same gaps and more often than not it's
going to fill in the same gaps even
across different tools which is
interesting. We have got for you an edit
request. Okay. And I'd like to see where
you take this. Okay. Macy's giggling
which makes me feel nervous. The
ceremony of the envelope. I love it.
Add natural disasters at least two.
super interesting because it was part of
my original game. So, it' be quite
fascinating to see how Simon's dealt
with this. I feel like Simon had a bit
of an advantage because you had added
the concept of like events already did
it. On the other hand, the code was in a
different state. Interesting. So, it has
doesn't seem to have the concept. Oh,
no. There is a hospital. There's no fire
department. So what kind of natural I
guess the natural disasters are going to
impact the happiness score and the
treasury. So things that make people sad
and make us lose money. What else even
is there? Would it affect the
population? My god, I guess it could
negatively impact the population.
So yeah, maybe there's I guess a health
outbreak. There's a natural disaster you
could have that could resolve itself
over time, but maybe initially just
something that has an immediate impact
to happiness or treasury. Maybe
something a little more approachable.
What's going to make people unhappy? Oh,
what if there's like an earthquake that
destroys some of the buildings? I love
that. Interesting. All right, let's just
start with that initial initial brief.
And you're using Windsurf for this. And
you haven't used it before? Using
Windsurf. Not used it before. No. Just
to get the project set up here. I am a
regular cursor user though, so this
looks reasonably familiar. So, I'm not
even going to look at any of the code.
I'm just going to say maybe I'll give it
a bit of a brief. This project is a tiny
town simulator that maintains a treasury
amount, happiness score, and users can
place different buildings in the town
that impact these figures as days
progress. Probably don't need to explain
it. It can read the code and understand
it, but there might be a layer of
indirection here. So, I'm just trying to
steer it a little bit. I want to add a
system whereby natural disasters happen
at random intervals. I wonder how it
will interpret random intervals. Yeah.
In the code, I want to be able to easily
adjust how often these occur. To start
with, there is only one type of natural
disaster, which is an earthquake that
affects a subset of the grid.
any building in this subset of the grid
gets destroyed and the following day it
disappears. Oh, interesting. Seems
reasonable. So then like it will have
some I'm expecting it to have some sort
of broken state like the building is
destroyed and then the next day it's
gone and it's cleared the way and you
can put a new building there if you
want. Nice. I feel like it will I want
to see if it knows to affect happiness
and treasury also. We'll figure that
out. So, I'm not expecting it to affect
treasury. You could say clearing the
stuff away is going to cost money, but
you've already spent the money on the
building and the building's gone now.
Oh, yeah. That's You could say it cost
more money. That's true. Happiness I
would definitely expect happiness to go
down. I would expect the population to
go down because each of these buildings
has this has five people in it. This has
20. Maybe they're not all home. Okay.
So, I can see it's got some stream of
thought here. I'll help you implement
the natural disaster system. So, we're
getting past the safeguards of these
LMs, which is good. So, first it's doing
a bit of exploration. It's interesting.
It's just saying, "Let me read this
file. Let me read this file, which is on
the one hand, it's nice to see the the
thought progression. On the other hand,
it doesn't help me in any way. I guess
it makes me feel more confident that it
knows what it's doing." So, based on the
codebased exploration, I understand that
we need to add a natural disaster system
that can randomly trigger earthquakes,
implement logic. Okay. So, it's just
said what I said back. That was it. I
didn't even realize it was still
working. So, we've been doing this for a
little bit. So, yeah. So, it spent a
bunch of time just figuring out what to
do and then it said what I'm going to do
is what you've asked me. So, it's
created a new file natural disasters.js
for which is a great file name.
Earthquake frequency 10% chance per day
of an earthquake occurring, which in a
in real life would be very scary. Feel
like I'm back in San Francisco. And this
code seems yeah, probably reasonable.
There's a loop in a loop which looks fun
to work with. Has it like has it stacked
a bunch of changes on top? I'm confused.
Yeah, I'm a bit confused by this diff.
It seems it looks to me like it's
keeping all this code and then it's
removing but this is at the top. This is
like the imports. This is the top of the
file. It's just rewritten it and the
diff is horrible. It's Yeah, possible.
So maybe what I'll do is I'll just
blindly accept everything because I have
such faith. I'm going to ignore all the
lint errors because I did notice when I
imported this there was a huge amount of
lint errors which is a nightmare. So
it's still working actually.
Interesting. So it's in some sort of
iteration loop here because it's saying
now I'm going to modify it to visualize
the earthquake. Now I'm going to fix
some issues. Now I'm going to fix some
lint issues. So maybe what was happening
I was viewing a diff that was out of
date and it was changing in an
unpredictable way. Oh, see that's I
don't know how user friendly that is.
Yeah, it's a bit hard to tell what
exactly is going on here. Guess I'm just
watching it. is explaining. Well, but
that's almost the problem. It's like
it's drawing your attention to these
things because it needs a human in the
loop, but it's also not ready yet. Yeah.
Like I can't do anything here. Like it's
still going. This is make a cup of tea
territory. It's trying to fix the lint
error. Trying to fix the lint errors,
which might seeen as there were so many
initially, it might just send it down a
might be a disaster. Does it still
compile? It looks like it's It currently
is. It was in a broken state a minute
ago to be fair. Like if it takes 10
minutes and then it makes the code
beautiful. I could Yeah, it's nice that
if I was like rapidly prototyping
something here, which is the aim, I
would like to be able to say, "Hey,
don't worry about linting and stuff so
much. I just want to get something
working." It's maybe a little over ego,
like a junior engineer that really keen
to impress, which is cool. Finally
finished. So, it said random earthquakes
going to occur at the end of each day,
10% chance. Random area of the grid, two
to four cells in size. I should up
increase the upper band of that to make
it more fun. Oh, visual feedback with a
shaking red overlay. That sounds like
fun. The system, it very confidently
says the system is now complete and
working, which I'm really interested to
find out. That's true. You can adjust
the earthquake frequency and size. So,
10% chance. Let's Oh, we can't. We
actually don't have a progress to the
next day, do we? Cuz that happens
automatically. Oh, no. Don't tell me.
Yeah. So, it's doesn't look very much
like it's working. I'm going to try
restart the server. Has it nuked it?
Seems like the natural disasters impact
is
larger than expected. But interestingly,
what has it actually changed here? Okay,
it's added a bunch of stuff to this town
grid thing for dealing with Yeah, the
cells and clicking on the cells. Okay,
it's added an animation for the
earthquake effect, which I really want
to see. Does it need an MPM install?
Maybe. Has it done anything new? hasn't
changed the dependencies as far as I can
tell. And there's package lock change,
but that's just cuz I installed npm
installed. The code seems there's
nothing standing out. And curiously,
there's no errors. There any front end
errors? Aha. Cannot access handle end
day before
initialization
simulator.jsx. So, I'm into debugging
territory now. So, that error appears.
Oh, there's a diff. Do I need to accept
all of this? Accept all. Oh, just
blindly accept it all. I assumed that it
just made the changes because it did
seem like it's made some of the changes
at least. Yeah. Yeah. No, I'm with you.
I didn't see that. And this doesn't
Although, weirdly, it didn't give you a
compilation error or anything. No, I'm
somewhat confused now cuz it seemed on
the one hand I had to accept stuff and
on the other hand, it's already
accepted. This is now not showing a
diff, but it's in changes, but it's a
brand new file. Okay, so we're still
getting the same error. Simulator.jsx.
So, I'm just going to go to
simulator.jsx and ask this thing to
there's a front end error coming from
this. Yeah. No, it also says here right
above the chat, zero files with changes
and yet there are a lot of diffs
showing. There's a lot happening in the
working tree which seems like is that
true or not? Yeah, I'm a bit confused
about the state of and this is an
interesting thing about these kind of
editors is you almost have like on top
of git there's now like a new layer of
working copy. It's like a change that's
been suggested and my understanding of
those things usually is when you accept
it becomes part of your change that you
can that's in your working copy and then
you can commit and there's some internal
state management but that does not
appear to be working well. Yes. So that
does seem like a reasonable fix for the
error. I'm slightly alarmed that it's
changed so many other things as well.
Okay, I know. Here's the fix for this
bug. This is interesting. It says,
"Here's the this is why this happens.
I'm going to fix it." And then it says,
"Oh, I see the issue." So, are there two
issues or has it fixed it twice? Yeah,
that's confusing. It's a very confusing
stream of consciousness. And it just
seems to be taking upon itself to make
unsolicited changes, which may be for
the better, but with these kind of
thing, I'm trying to like scope down the
the scope of each change. So, what I
could maybe do if this doesn't work is
start again with a smaller brief. Like
maybe ask it to write this kind of style
file for dealing with a part of it and
then I could like layer on the UI part
and layer on the other part. But that's
me like adapting the workflow to help
the LLM, I suppose. Yeah, I think it's
not a bad shout though. But I also don't
think that you asked for anything
insane. It wasn't like it wasn't like a
list of five things you wanted changed.
just like add the concept of this.
Sometimes we see at work that when we're
overly prescriptive, it actually has the
reverse effect. It's this is oversp
specified and that will also make for a
bad program. I don't feel like you did
that. You let it do its thing. You gave
it an open-ended thing and it's it seems
to really be struggling. And this is the
point, I think, of these this kind of
workflow, right? that can edit multiple
files and hold like a bunch of context
in its in the window a single time. And
I wouldn't expect to have to break the
problem down into unless I was very
opinionated about what the design should
be. I want to have this file for
managing this stuff and this file for
managing this stuff. I would expect they
could fill in the gaps and get it
working. I wonder if it's getting
tripped up because there's so many
issues. I wonder if I just remove the
ESLint and say, "Look, I don't care
about linting." I think that's a good
idea. And just for people listening like
this, it really is in a bit of a loop.
So it's now sad. I see the issue. I see
the issue. I see the issue. I see the
issue. JSX edited simulator searched
codebase for the same function. Then
again, I see the issue now. We have
duplicate declarations. I feel like we
barely got started here. So I've deleted
the ESLint config in the hopes that this
will make the editor understand that I
don't care about linting. And I've
canled this confusing loop. Don't if I
can change if I can clear this context
window. Okay, start a new conversation.
Where do we get to terribly far? Okay,
so we're going to try and fix this
again. So in simulator. So now we're
asking for help to like actually fix fix
this one by introduced because our thing
still isn't rendering which is sad.
Exactly. If this does a better job then
it might be that if we'd done the
original amend after we deleted the
ESLint config then that would be good.
But it is curious that base 44 has
generated an application with quite an
extensive ESLint configuration and the
code that it has made is not compliant
with that eslint configuration by any
means necessary. There's a bunch of lint
errors raises the question of what's the
point? Well yeah why even add it? But
then also like because it's such a
closed environment, I'm sure in their
case like they just don't it just gives
gener maybe if it's like a leftover
artifact they obviously don't suffer
with the same issue. No, but it's like
maybe they're opinionated that this is a
good thing to have in a project to keep
it clean, which is true, but only if you
actually write code in that way. Yeah,
exactly. Why give us more work? Okay, so
it seems to have found itself in a loop
again. I notice there's a duplicate
declaration of handle end day in the
file. I see that handle in day is
defined twice. I feel like I might need
to intervene here and do some manual
fixing because it might not even be that
I have a suspicion about what's going on
here that I can't necessarily prove. But
I think what might be happening is it
goes through this loop. It finds
something that's wrong, fixes it, then
analyzes its own diff and then is like
there's two declarations of this. Oh,
interesting. Yes, because you have just
written just did that. Yeah.
Interesting. It seem because it does
seem to be upset about its own diff
which is a real issue. And at this point
it's like why don't I just manually I'm
going to see if I can manually fix this.
Get rid of one. Yeah. Basically this
function handle end day. It's called
here but it was defined further down. So
I'm going to make it the first of these
block of functions. Nice. possible
that's introduced more bugs, but let's
see. Okay, so same thing with handle
delete building, which is frustrating.
So, it's got the order of these things
wrong. It's a pretty basic thing,
but okay. All right, I think we're back.
Oh, we're back. We're back. Amazing.
Notable that that took me like two
seconds to just fix myself, but I was
interested in getting the LM to fix it
for me. Yes. Very notable. What state
are we in now? What are we expecting to
happen? We're expecting that there's a
10% chance each day of a earthquake
happening. So perhaps what I should do
is I raise that to 70% to actually test
whether this is happening. I'm going to
make that 80%. Yeah, I can immediately
see Joe's gone straight to the code to
do that because I think we're I don't
trust the other anymore. Feeling a
little ky about the chat. Yeah. So yeah,
I'm expecting it said there's some
shaking animation which I'm interested
to see if it's done a good job. Yeah,
I'm going to put some more buildings.
What's the cheapest building? A small
house. Now, the remind me the earthquake
is meant to happen like in couple of
squares. Yeah, an area between two to
four squares assuming squared. Okay, I
see. So, you've kind of battleshipped
your houses to catch the earthquake.
Spent all my money here, but it should
be an 80% chance. So, I could change it
to 100% chance to really keep things
moving here as well. Okay, 100%. Oh,
that's nice. It suggested the comment.
That was a very fast autocomplete. Okay,
so when this day ends, there should be
an earthquake somewhere. Okay, five.
It's quite alarming.
Yeah, I'm nervous.
Interesting. And the animation is
actually pretty is pretty good. Are
pretty good at generating CSS animation
code, it turns out. Yeah, I'm actually
impressed by that. And it it scared me.
So that's a good measure of success
there. Yes. But it somehow managed to
hit an area of the map where I don't
have any buildings, which it's quite
impressive. I thought you did have one
there. Oh, maybe. Maybe. I thought I
didn't. Unless it disappeared
immediately and that midnight. I didn't
see it. Okay. Everyone pay special
attention now. Okay. I was looking at
happiness and it went down only 1%. Oh,
interesting. Is that just because
happiness just generally goes down over
time, though? I think it does.
Wow. There's a story there about life.
Simon coded it. So, we'll chat about
that at the end. Oh, there we go. Yes.
So, I did disappeared. The house
disappeared. It did. If I was
nitpicking, the house disappeared
immediately. I was expecting it to be
like broken for a day and then
disappear, but that doesn't really
matter. It didn't have its broken state.
Now, what happened with your money? So,
happiness definitely went down.
Happiness went down. Is it going down
all the time? We should check. Money
didn't go down, but you can imagine a
world where that kind of makes sense.
like the cleanup cost we can maybe
factor that in. I would be bankrupt now.
Did population change? What we'd have
these take? So this is 20 and then this
is okay. So the population should be 40
which means that the earthquake didn't
kill anyone but they're now unhoused.
Oh, I see. But I didn't prompt it to be
murderous earthquake. So that seems
fair. Okay, here comes another happiness
went down again. unclear whether it went
down just because of the day but I have
changed it to 100% money which is
definitely wrong. I think that's just
because these buildings earn me money
every day. Oh yeah. Okay, fine. So your
rate of money is going down. Yeah,
that's very true. Actual treasury isn't
being affected. Very true. Very true.
Okay, so we've got some natural
disasters, but it does say at least two.
I've only got one type of natural
disaster. What's one you could add in
two minutes? What about rather than it
being like one of these burns down, what
if it's like a lightning strike that is
like a single square, a single house, a
single square gets hit and yeah, it's
like battleships, right? And then it'll
be interesting to see what new like
design it comes up for this. Okay, so
let's see. I'm going to commit this
stuff. Oh, smart. Real developers.
It's conventional commit there as well.
Cool. All right, let's start a new chat.
Add a new natural disaster for lightning
strikes. A lightning strike affects a
single square on the grid. And if there
is a building in this square, it gets
destroyed. Happiness goes down when
lightning strikes. Oh, and it goes down
more if a building is destroyed. I'll
let it figure out what numbers it likes.
create a cool
animation for the lightning similar to
the one we have for earthquakes. Make
the frequency of lightning configurable.
I would be interested to make it not
just happen at the end of the day, but
to happen throughout the day, but I I
don't want to overload at this point.
Yeah, I feel like our trust is fragile
with this thing, unfortunately. And I'm
going to be watching it like a hot cuz
last time it
just seemed to mess everything up and
took ages. I did get in a really
confused little loop in it. So, it's
examining the existing natural disasters
implementation even though it just wrote
it, but it is a new chat. Yeah. Again,
like the context management for these
tools I think is fascinating. What an
easy job Simon must have had. Already
had this all implemented, but not
working. Yeah. I'm curious. I want him
to tell you about some of the things
that he did. A different approach as
well. This is like a reasonable approach
I think what it's doing here. Yeah, it
seems credible so far what it's done
here. This component is getting really
big and complicated. So I think its
likelihood of confusing itself is high.
Oh, I can see it's made this a bit more
generic. I can see it's animation. It's
chosen a fade in. Yeah. Yeah. Fade in
and out. By the looks of it, it does
look like it's got less confuse than it
did last time. So far, it does feel like
it's got has got quite a bit less to do
now. That's true. It's already got all
the scaffolding. It's got the concept of
random disasters. This is always seems
to be taking longer than expected. It's
interesting that it said yes to itself.
It's in this like weird sort of speaking
to itself mode. Oh my god. I need to
check. Oh yes, we do need to do that.
Okay, it's made the changes. I can't
read that. But now we need to remember
to accept. I'm going to blindly accept.
But again, I noticed that it's already
in my working copy. I don't think accept
actually does anything other than tell
windf that I'm happy with it. Whereas I
imagine reject would revert these files.
So again, it's not committing it. Not
committing. It is making the change to
the file. So it appears in my working
copy. Yeah. But so accept I think is
like a noop. Doesn't do anything. It
just allows this to understand that I'm
happy. Okay. So there's no errors which
is good. I'm going to increase the
chance of lightning to 100%. Oh, I've
lost some more buildings actually since
we last looked at this. But I don't have
anywhere near enough for any interesting
buildings. But can you increase houses
speed of the day? Oh, interesting to be
like I'm searching seconds.
Oh, yeah. 60, isn't it? Lots of things
are 60. Yeah. Is that obvious? Time
left. Oh, here we go. But I think that
Yeah, there's a magic number that's used
in a few places. God, I hate when they
do that. That's a really common LM. It
did an earthquake.
Okay. Do I need to reduce that to 0%
chance? Okay. Let me go into simulator
and I tell you what, I'll do that in a
new chat just in case. Okay, cool. I
like making some changes. It seemed to
gro that immediately. I feel like the
issue before was just it was a
complicated thing that we asked. I
wonder if Windsor like do they
specifically advertise that they're
better at targeted changes rather than
sweeping changes? Interesting. Not sure.
I would say cursor is pretty good at
sweeping changes. I must admit it's not
really part of my workflow so much like
doing these like big add this feature
kind of thing in the in my day-to-day.
I'm more kind of thinking how I'd break
down the problem and give the LLM
smaller problems because I'm working in
a code base I'm much more familiar with
and there's established patterns and
things like that. Maybe I'm missing a
trick there. I wouldn't say so. I'm sure
you're making like much more targeted
changes and you're able to explain with
some precision. Whereas this is there's
no test. There's no rubric. It's just
Oh, okay. Let's see. Aha, there you go.
There's lightning. It's decided to
impact two squares by the looks of it.
It has. It's picked two squares. The
animation is cool. It could be that the
logic is only one square, but it's got
the size of the thing wrong. I suppose
it would be difficult for us to test
that. Only got enough money for two more
houses. I believe I just saw in the code
actually that I think this is in local
storage. I might be able to I'm going to
give myself a lot more money. Oh wow.
Oh, is that how you do it?
Fantastic.
Cool. Let's go spending. Interesting
that it thinks it thinks the power
plants take up four but only visually
takes up one. I like the idea of a
building being able to take up more
space. That's cool. I think that's a
cool detail. Put some parks around.
Interesting that we might need to put a
little exception for parks. Lightning
shouldn't destroy an entire park. Or
maybe it will. Guess it depends on the
brutal. It seems to be your style. Why
is happiness so bad? Oh, it's because of
the power plants. Uh yeah, yeah, yeah.
Bad news. And there's lightning every
night.
They just had 50 earthquakes in a month.
This town is having a real tough time.
Starting to rebuild though would be such
a shame if I wonder how I wonder if
there's a minimum cap on the happiness.
My happiness is at zero. I've got a 0%
approval rating in this town, which is
fair enough. It's mostly power plants.
One one poor house, two houses. You
weren't elected. Oh, there goes the
light. All right. Get destroyed. There
wasn't anything in that gap by the looks
of it. But assuming that it works, I'm
pretty happy with it. There's 70 people
living here, which um I don't know where
they're all going to live because
there's two condos and one house. Z
index always fun. They should honestly
leave. Yeah, this is my opinion. This is
not the kind of town you want to live
in, I think. No, but I will say Joe, I
think you you nailed it. You did two
natural disasters. We had a bunch of
FAF, didn't we? But we did. You did it.
Congrats. Good job. Thanks. That was
good fun. Okay, let's bring Simon back
here and debrief. Sounds good. That was
so fun. So, you guys ended up with
projects that I feel were pretty
similar, but you took very different
paths to get there. And importantly, you
used two new tools each, which is crazy.
Yeah. How did you find them? I really
enjoyed B 44. Actually, as a Bolt user,
I saw a lot of similarities. I felt like
B 44 got me to what I wanted much much
quicker. Although to be honest, watching
the way you had to take my code and all
the dependencies that it required into B
44 was actually really frustrating. But
I really had a good time with B 44 in
and generating the doing the prototype
time. How about you? It was good fun. I
found the sort of 0ero to one like going
from a short little brief into pretty
useful and well-designed app was quite
impressive. It's a bit like Uncanny
Valley in that it's a bit like an IDE,
but a lot of the IDE functionality isn't
there. So, I found myself like going to
use things like command click on
something, but that's not working, which
is a bit weird, but I guess maybe I'm a
bit more of a power user. I definitely
imagine it is something that will be
helpful the next time a friend or a
family member asks me, oh, can you help
me make this app? There's something for
that. Disposable apps, disposable code.
It's very nice for that kind of use. And
I saw you struggled a little bit with
Oh, wow. I'm looking at your screen.
There's lightning happening all over the
place. It's terrible. Yeah. created a
very poor town. They're having a real
hard time. How about with windfur? And
that's I've not used Windsor. I
typically stick with cursor just because
I've used it a fair amount. How about
you then with Windsor? Would you how did
you like that as a power cursor user
yourself? Yeah. Yeah. Pretty similar. A
lot of the same kind of concepts.
Everyone's coming up with like fun names
for the chat thing going on in the
sidebar, but the interaction model feels
very similar. I'd say that I probably
used it in a way that I wouldn't
normally use a cursor like in my
day-to-day work for example where I'd
think about something break the problem
down and scope the changes a little more
localized whereas here I was just I
don't know this code base I don't want
to understand it I want you to implement
this whole sweeping feature so maybe a
bit tricky to compare them but yeah I
found the management of the state of my
changes tricky to figure out like at
what point is it actually editing the
files on disk and at what point is it
showing me a suggestion of something
that will edit which I think is a common
problem that they also have in cursor.
That's exacerbated if you're working on
a big problem and it's taking a long
time. I can't also be refactoring
something else because then I have a mix
of a bunch of different things going on
and that makes my commit history a
nightmare. I found cursor as a cursor
user myself. I wasn't learning anything
new per se in in doing this. I found it
extremely hard to take it to that next
level and to actually build on top of it
because every time I was in that
horrible frustrating loop where I want
to make a change, it says it's made it
but actually I'm seeing further problems
or the same the same output.
Interesting. And then I'm constantly in
this loop of actually this didn't
happen. Can you fix it? Yeah, I fixed
it. Oh, it's still a problem. Can you
fix it? There's still the problem. And
that was very frustrating. But that's
the classic prototype quick fix issue.
Maybe that is a bit of a difference with
Windsurf because it did seem to want to
try and fix problems and actually that
in itself became a problem that the app
that you delivered had an ESLint
configuration but a lot of the code had
loads of violations of that eslint
configuration. So my interpretation was
that Windsurf was getting in a loop of
oh I notice all these lint issues I'm
going to fix them. I notice all these
lint issues I'm going to fix them even
though it hadn't introduced them. So
it's nice that it's trying to respect
the configuration of the environment and
keep things clean. But yeah, it was a
particular case where it confused the
hell out of out of wind surf and we had
to remove the incident configuration
entirely so that it stopped trying to
keep it at this quality bar that it
wasn't at originally. I felt a little
bad, Joe, that I think in both cases you
got maybe the short straw. very harsh to
say about these tools, but Simon was
able to get to a working prototype
basically immediately in base 44 and you
really didn't spend any time debugging
in base 44. In fact, you did not even
look at the code like we we looked to
see that it was there. Yeah. But did not
read it at all. There's just no need.
Whereas Joe immediately got into this
asked for virtually the same thing,
right? But immediately got into this
loop. And you'll love my first prompt as
well because I I started writing down
some ideas of these are the things that
I think we need and I'm thinking Sim
City and then I then I got to the prompt
and I'm just like I was about to type in
a whole bunch and I'm like actually no
there are five words I need and it was
the exact five words Macy wrote on the
true brief and it came back with this it
took a while and I was getting a little
bit worried. took. In fact, Macy, you
probably saw both. I think Base 44 and
my experience with Bolt took a lot
longer than Bolt would have done if I
prompted it in exactly the same way. But
once it did come back, it was I'm going
to say solid from the point of view that
as a prototype app, it worked and
clicking around didn't actually create
too many issues. It just worked. I think
I'll have to look back on it, but I
think I probably used five prompts or
fewer to get it to this point, which is
surprising. It just kind of just took a
large amount of time and I was like
given the prompts that Macy gave me was
so short. I kind of like pretty much hit
that within the first prompt that I gave
base 44. Yeah, the problems I guess if
we think about it from the team point of
view and everyone's using B 44. It
started putting adding in or it started
adding in its own kind of persistence
layer and it wasn't per perhaps I in
hindsight I would I would potentially
kind of add from the start don't add
your own authentication. don't add your
don't use your own persistence models.
In fact, for those listening, I did had
to I did have to go offline and make my
own changes to say use local persistence
and things like that so that you could
continue. So, yeah, very interesting.
Yeah, there's a bunch of that kind of
lock in out the gate with base 44. And I
think with these kind of things, they
work well when you're not super
opinionated on you have a great example
there. You wanted some sort of town
simulator, but you weren't super
opinionated about the features that it
had. And in some ways that's really
helpful to like think creatively to
expand the scope. But if you're coming
to these tools with a strong idea of the
kind of thing that you want to build and
exactly how you want that to look and
work, it's a bit of a different story.
And it's interesting actually. So did
your environment use local persistence
or local. I don't know because I
couldn't get the state management to
work. I think it was just like like
within memory essentially. So if you
refresh it would lose it, but I can't
quite remember. And it was unclear
because it wasn't working. Yeah. Cuz I
was surprised actually thinking about
it. it wouldn't use superbase which is
actually say for those who aren't
familiar with bolt superbase netifi
other zero friction paths to do these
kinds of things so it although it
wouldn't be a similar lock in in terms
of the same base 44 I'm surprised it
didn't just try to go oh do you want to
use super base as your persistence layer
and things like that I was quite
surprised at how fast we could get to
this prototype particularly with base 44
before I was quite surprised at how hard
it was to get further with cursor with
your environment hitting that many
problems. But yeah, I think there's been
a fair amount of magic on show today.
Were you able to get mine my state
management working? To be honest,
similar to how I've experienced your
code in the past here, I wasn't able to
progress your application any further
than I don't really. So that is
unfortunate. I that's because I didn't
handwrite it. But yeah,
something that's interesting that when
we were imagining what we'd do for this
episode, we imagined that you both would
do this and neither of you did this and
that's ask Curser or Winter or whoever
for an overview of the code. How what is
this and how does it work? Interesting.
Both of you had the exact same process
which was like maybe a little impeded in
your case, Joe. it was to get the thing
running without really looking up
without examining any more that he
needed to and then just diving into the
edits. There's really I just we didn't
anticipate necessarily that would be the
process. It's interesting workflow wise
like in a codebase I don't really care
about the quality of it and I need to
make quick changes and I like I'm just
here to add features not to maintain
this nice garden of code. Why do I even
need to understand it? If the if I can
get the LLM to do the changes for me and
I can validate that they at least seem
to work in the browser, it's enough for
this exercise. I agree. And I think
actually it was probably for the sake of
brevity that I didn't think about it too
much in terms of I actually thought as
well I was talking with Dion actually
while you were doing yours and I thought
actually what I'll probably do straight
away is I'll ask her tell me about this
but actually once I got there I just
thought I don't need to I know what I
want to do and probably we're all under
time pressures so we'll probably do
something similar even in a real world
situation to some extent but what I
really liked in your example was you
tried to give a context text. The very
first thing that you did was describe
what the application did, which is
really interesting. I'd love to kind of
understand maybe with and without that
if it would actually have done it
differently, had that just assumption
that use this app as your context. You
should already know this in more detail
than I could provide you with. And it's
fun how you were trying to tell it what
it was doing given that you hadn't even
looked at the code as well. So, you're
doing it from a very high level of
trying to explain to it when it probably
knew it better than you did at the time.
Very true. It seems crazy, but my
rationale was that it can see the code,
but it can't like see the interface. I
wanted to like give it a little bit I
want to give it some eyes intent. Yeah,
here's all this code, but what's the
point in it? What is this driving? Yeah,
I have no no data on whether that helps
or not. It just intuitively like I'm
working with this thing that's blind to
one whole aspect. Yeah. So, I have a
final question for Simon. So towards the
end of Joe's prototyping, he did
something unrelated to the functionality
of the app, which was designed to maybe
throw you off course a little bit. Can
you do you have any guesses as to what
that was? Was it obvious? Designed to
throw I see he design he did something
to his app that was designed to throw me
off course. Interesting. I can't think
of anything that would throw me off.
What did he do? It did get scoped down.
It did get scoped down quite
significantly. Really? Now I can't
think. I can't think. What was it? I
felt bad. So, initially my first
instinct was to ask it to make the code
as illeible by a human as possible. Turn
it into something that looks like
compiled code. Yeah. But considering the
app wasn't even working, I thought that
was a really unfair handicap. So
instead, I asked it to replace like
function and variable names with funny
and misleading names. Um, and we were
right pushing up on time here. And I
don't think it did a good job. LM's
maybe not great interpreters of the word
funny, but that's almost a little bit
dangerous because it's using that as
context, so it would almost confuse
itself a little bit with that
potentially. Um, interesting. I thought
you were going to name the town Beijing
Stoke and I completely missed it, but
that's interesting. That's an even
better. I I jokingly said I was going to
obiscate the code for you at one point,
but no, which is fine anyway because
neither of us really looked at the code
anyway, apart from you have no various
troubles with with it. I wonder how
whether that would have thrown the LLM
off if it's dealing with super obiscated
code or whether it would just be able to
figure it out. Yeah. Yeah. I have to say
it's choice like one of the choices it
made was it renamed the variable initial
state to initial chaos. Yeah. Oh, I did
see that
initial chaos is you just didn't even it
did clock and I thought oh my god if I
bring this up would it sound stupid? But
there was something in my mind where I
was like initial chaos why would there
be cha Yeah. That's it. That is really
interesting. Yeah, I'm gonna have to
maybe not the funniest twist. No, I did
want to push that a little further, but
running out of time there. I should have
done it in another language. Should have
said change everything to French or
something. Awesome. That was fun for me.
We hoped to time box this in an hour. We
did it in just over three with lots of
tweaking and stuff off air. Thank you
everyone for listening. This is a very
different style session to to that we
normally do. We hope it was interesting
to you. We hope it was good fun to
introduce maybe one or two new tools
across the four that we showed today.
And yeah, thanks for watching and
listening and tune in to the next
session. Thanks very much. Bye for
[Music]
[Applause]
now. Thanks for tuning in. Join us next
time on the AI Native Dev brought to you
by Tesla.